Guide to the John D. Mattox Papers
John D. Mattox Papers
- Extended Family Photographs
  - Edward playing Wash Tub with Orchestra, church assembly room (neg) (Box 2)
  - Linda's Birthday (neg), July 1960 (Box 2)
  - Mamma - Portrait made in Atlanta (neg) (Box 2)
  - Portraits of Vernon Mattox's Children (neg) (Box 2)
  - Bonnie Sue (neg), Aug 1962 (Box 2)
  - Portrait - John Roberts (little boy) (Print), May 1954 (Box 2)
  - Portrait - John Roberts (little boy) (neg), May 1954 (Box 2)
  - Aunt Jenny Knott Portrait (Print), March 9, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Aunt Jenny Knott Portrait (neg), March 9, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Marsh Knott Portrait (neg) (Box 2)
  - Douglas & Hubert around table - Wilson (neg) (Box 2)
  - Bruce Knott Portrait (Print), Aug 15, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Johnny David Mattox (Print), circa 1964 (Box 2)
  - Johnny David Mattox (neg), circa 1964 (Box 2)
  - Passport - Vernon Mattox (neg), Dec 3, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Annie Sue Faison (neg), July 1953 (Box 2)
  - Grandmother Bain (neg), July 1953 (Box 2)
  - Mary & Geo. Bruce (neg) (Box 2)
  - Vernon Mattox Portrait (neg), Feb 1951 (Box 2)
  - Jim, Laurie, & Baby (neg) (Box 2)
  - Marsh Kott(?) paying ins. checks (neg), July 14, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Annie Sue Class Reunion (neg), June 1967 (Box 2)
  - Jeannett, Bonnie Sue, & Herbert in front of house is Banville, Va. (neg), Aug 5, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Grandmother & her sisters, Douglas Bains house (neg), July 19, 1953 (Box 2)
  - Portrait - Little Bill, Edward Mattox, Raleigh (Print), Sept 28, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Portrait - Little Bill, Edward Mattox, Raleigh (neg), Sept 28, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Martha Roberts Class Reunion (neg), July 1958 (Box 2)
  - Bill Griffin Class of 1928 Reunion, Wendell (neg), May 24, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Massie Faison, Gus Faison grave (neg), Sept 20, 1955 (Box 2)
  - Portrait - Nellie Mattox Wedding Announcement (neg) (Box 2)
  - Lonnie Knot Portrait (neg), Oct 31, 1953 (Box 2)
  - R.L. & Alma Mattox 75th Anniversary (neg) (Box 2)
  - Elbert Holmes portrait (neg) (Box 2)
  - Vernon, Nellie, & Children (neg), June 1959 (Box 2)
  - Lonnie Knott Portrait (neg), Aug 27, 1962 (Box 2)
  - Lonnie Knott Portrait (Print), Aug 27, 1962 (Box 2)
  - John Roberts Graduation Portraits (neg), June 1968 (Box 2)
  - John Roberts Graduation Portraits (Print), June 1968 (Box 2)
  - Portrait - Marion Bain (neg), Dec 9, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Portrait - Marion Bain (Print), Dec 9, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Pa Mattox Portrait (neg) (Box 2)
  - Jo, Jim, Sue, & Riley Mattox (neg) (Box 2)
  - Copy of Bain Booklet - from Mama's booklet & Kathleen pages from Archives & History (neg), Nov 23, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Mary's family - Mother, Father, & Children copies (neg) (Box 2)
  - Davis Uncles, Granddad, Miss Edna, Mr. Lawrence, coat of arms, copies (neg), Aug 1970 (Box 2)
  - Grandmother, Aunt Martha, copies (neg) (Box 2)
  - Aunt Bertie (Beula Roberta Knott) about age 20 (neg), copied 1964 (Box 2)
  - Mattox Family, Mother's Day 1952, At Annie Sue's house on Cemetary Rd (neg) (Box 2)
  - Wasdon Family portraits (Print), circa late 1800s (Box 2)
  - Mrs. Davis Portrait, copy (Print) (Box 2)
  - Annie Lilly (Grandmother Bain) (Print), copied 1980 (Box 2)
  - Annie Lilly (Grandmother Bain) (neg), copied 1980 (Box 2)
  - Daddy & Dan (Mattox's father) (neg), copy May 1975 (Box 2)
  - Mama portrait (Mattox's mother) (neg), Dec 1963 (Box 2)
  - Daddy's grave (neg) (Box 2)
  - Daddy & Dan, Mamma on Pony, copies (neg) (Box 2)
  - Johnny Mattox graduation (neg), 1966 (Box 2)
  - Vernon Mattox Birthday Dinner (neg), Feb 27, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Baines & Grandma at Women's Club, Wendell, N.C. (neg) (Box 2)
  - Johnny (Grandpa) & Ernestine Mattox home (Print) (Box 5)
  - Group pictures, possibly from family reunion (Print) (Box 5)
  - Mary Davis and siblings (neg) (Box 5)
  - Mary Davis and siblings (Print) (Box 5)
  - Mattox children - Jim, Vernon, Edward, Jeanett (Copy) (Print) (Box 5)
  - Mattox children - Jim, Vernon, Edward, Jeanett (neg) (Box 5)
  - Ben & Johnny Mattox; Mattox's father & Father Walston (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Wendell, NC Photographs
  This series contains photographs of various locations and events in Mattox’s hometown of Wendell, North Carolina. Buildings include churches, schools, banks, and businesses. School functions like graduations and homecomings and church activities are also included. This series also contains portraits made by Mattox of people who lived in Wendell. Interesting items include a set of glass plate negatives depicting town scenes circa the late 1920s.
  - Mr. Cash in field & Jake Mays barns, Hail Damage, Tobacco, Hail & Tornado damage at Wendell (neg), July 5, 1954 (Box 4)
  - Graduating Class & Mascot (Doug) (neg), 1952 (Box 4)
  - Douglas - Junior High graduating class commencement and class day (neg), June 1962 (Box 4)
  - Library dedication - Mary & Douglas with Globe (neg), March 5, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Mary Mattox, assistant librarian at Wendell Library (neg), July 29, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Wendell School Activities for Annual, Mary at front door (neg), Oct 1964 (Box 4)
  - Eclipse of sun, Wendell, N.C. (neg), March 7, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Wendell School shop (neg), about 1960 (Box 4)
  - Old Church building from glass negative, Wendell, N.C. (neg) (Box 4)
  - Bank of Wendell, Lake Glad (neg), Aug 12, 1956 (Box 4)
  - Hudson Belk, Farmers Warehouse (neg), May 1956 (Box 4)
  - Douglas - Senior Class mascot, Wendell (neg), May 26/27, 1953 (Box 4)
  - Old Church before going to new church (neg) (Box 4)
  - New church (neg), 1956 (Box 4)
  - Wendell Christian Church & Minister's home (neg), Oct 13, 1960 (Box 4)
  - New Christian Church, Wendell, N.C. - interior and back exterior (neg), March 11, 1951 (Box 4)
  - New Wendell Christian Church interior - ordered by Mack Roberts, Chamber of Commerce (neg), Aug 15, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Christian Church Landscaping (neg), April 2, 1951 (Box 4)
  - New Church being built (neg) (Box 4)
  - Installation of minister Rev. John Whidden - Wendell Christian Church (neg), July 24, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Installation of minister Rev. John Whidden - Wendell Christian Church (Print), July 24, 1960 (Box 4)
  - C.Y.F. Group at Church (neg), Feb 3, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Old Church - Sunday School groups (neg) (Box 4)
  - Harold Griffin presenting silver platter at church (neg) (Box 4)
  - Charter Members of Christian Church (Print), May 1980 (Box 4)
  - Charter Members of Christian Church (neg), May 1980 (Box 4)
  - Holiness Church in Old Christian Church, Street Sign at Entrance of Wall St. (neg), March 2, 1957 (Box 4)
  - Old Christian Church, inside front window (neg) (Box 4)
  - Classes at Old Christian Church (neg) (Box 4)
  - Rev. Jack Suggs portrait (neg) (Box 4)
  - Youth Conference at Christian Church, Missionary from Mexico in group (neg), April 14, 1953 (Box 4)
  - Walter Anderson portrait (for Doctorate publicity) (Print), May 21, 1965 (Box 4)
  - Walter Anderson portrait (for Doctorate publicity) (neg), May 21, 1965 (Box 4)
  - New Christian Church Wendell, N.C. - picture used for church bulletin (neg), Sept 25, 1960 (Box 4)
  - New Church Interior, Wendell, N.C. (neg), March 24, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Halloween Party at Church (neg), Oct 29, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Christian Church Interiors Business Meeting Sunday (neg), Oct 1960 (Box 4)
  - The Palms [sheet music] (neg), March 1953 (Box 4)
  - Rev. Allen Manuel portrait Christian Church Minister (Print), Aug 4, 1966 (Box 4)
  - Rev. Allen Manuel portrait Christian Church Minister (neg), Aug 4, 1966 (Box 4)
  - Bronze Plaque on Wendell Library (neg), about 1965 (Box 4)
  - Senator Scott at Wendell Lunch Room (neg), 1957 (Box 4)
  - Doug and other High School grads receiving Bibles at Church Walter Anderson, minister (neg) (Box 4)
  - Homecoming and Organ dedication (neg), Sept 6, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Edwards Wedding Christian Church (neg), Nov 1951 (Box 4)
  - Mary and Whiddens, young people - front of Christian tree (neg), 1960 (Box 4)
  - Annie Sue's Wedding Old Church - decorated interiors (neg) (Box 4)
  - Ivan Hinton, women's prison head (neg) (Box 4)
  - Homecoming Queen Wendell School (neg), Oct 26, 1962 (Box 4)
  - M. Faison - Group of men singing (neg) (Box 4)
  - Snow in Wendell, N.C. (neg), Jan 20, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Old Front - Hephzibah Church at night Wendell, N.C. (neg), May 14, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Veterans Banquet & Graduation (neg), Dec 19, 1957 (Box 4)
  - Veterans - Wendell (neg) (Box 4)
  - John Mattox house; Old Christian Church Building - before library repair began (neg), about 1957 (Box 4)
  - Phil Whitley, Planters Warehouse (neg), Dec 1958 (Box 4)
  - Johnson, Youdy, Mr. Brewer (neg), Oct 1976 (Box 4)
  - Golf Links at Wendell, Formal Opening (neg), 1960 (Box 4)
  - School Buildings - 1911 & High School (neg) (Box 4)
  - Bank of Wendell Opening (Print), July 1953 (Box 4)
  - Bank of Wendell Opening (neg), July 1953 (Box 4)
  - Bank of Wendell - 50th Anniversary Dinner (neg), April 1957 (Box 4)
  - Hudson Belk Store exterior (neg), Jan 2, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Proc's Service Station (neg), Aug 7, 1958 (Box 4)
  - Wendell Library construction (Print), Oct 1959 (Box 4)
  - Wendell Library - front & interiors (neg), 1962 (Box 4)
  - Maggie Hester, Old Richardson Farm House (neg), 1962 (Box 4)
  - Old Christian Church before repair for library (neg), Fall 1958 (Box 4)
  - Pure Oil Station, Traffic in front of Mattox House (neg), Feb 2, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Bank of Wendell (neg), May 17, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Banquet at Dolphin, Mrs. Bob Newell (neg), June 22, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Banquet at Dolphin, Mrs. Bob Newell (Print), June 22, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Hudson Belk Store Formal Opening (Doug & Mary Mattox in several photos) (neg) (Box 4)
  - Governor, Bo Todd, & Mrs. Perry (neg) (Box 4)
  - Hudson Belk (neg), Sept 13, 1953 (Box 4)
  - Hudson Belk Interior, Lyman Kyser-manager (neg), 1959 (Box 4)
  - Church group at Ferne Todd's House, Rev. Buck Baker (neg), Sept 27, 1958 (Box 4)
  - Proc Dean Service Station (new) (neg) (Box 4)
  - Bunny Vuderhill (?) Class Reunion (neg), June 1958 (Box 4)
  - Storage Houses for Tobacco, Ed Sykes (neg), Oct 11, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Wendell Fire Department & Douglas as Mascot (neg), March 12, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Homecoming Game, Wendell High School (neg), Oct 11, 1963 (Box 4)
  - Congressed Entrance to Wall St. (neg), March 2, 1957 (Box 4)
  - Broken Sidewalk, 307 Wall St (neg), July 1974 (Box 4)
  - Homecoming Queen & Football Game (neg), Oct 16, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Homecoming Queen & Football Game (Print), Oct 16, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Whitley Warehouse Perry's Store, Wendell, NC (Print) (Box 5)
  - Exterior of Wendell United Method Church (Print) (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Class & Graduation photos (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Whitley Warehouse - men with tobacco (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - Whitley Warehouse, Perry's Store, Wendell, N.C. (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - Church, Wendell, N.C. (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - Brick Building with Columns, Wendell, N.C. (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - Whitely Warehouse store front, Wendell, N.C. (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - Buildings in Wendell, N.C. (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - Streetview including Wendell Drug Co. (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - Train Station, Wendell, N.C. (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - Unidentified house with large porch probably in Wendell, N.C. (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - Interior of Tobacco Warehouse, Wendell, N.C. (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - The Farmers Warehouse storefront (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - Exterior of Wendell United Methodist Church (Glass Plate) (Box 9)
  - Buildings (Flatfolder 10)
- North Carolina State University Photographs
  This series contains photographs and slides of students and faculty, campus scenes, extension services, and the North Carolina State Fair. Several photographs show Mattox taking pictures or in his office in the Visual Aids Department. There are also images of the R.O.T.C. Glee Club, which Mattox directed. Other interesting images include Mattox’s fifty year class reunion in 1983, retirement banquets for Mattox, and campus publications featuring Mattox’s photographs.
  - John Masttox at Desk, Mrs. Neal and others in office (neg), Sept 7, 1960 (Box 3)
  - John Mattox at Desk in Ricks Hall (neg), about 1962 (Box 3)
  - Freshman John Mattox, NCSU, in ROTC uniform (neg), 1929 (Box 3)
  - John Mattox in reactor (neg), Feb 20, 1959 (Box 3)
  - John Mattox sitting on top edge of state fair coliseum with camera (neg), 1953 (Box 3)
  - John with camera (neg), 1953 (Box 3)
  - John Mattox at desk in Ricks Hall (neg) (Box 3)
  - John Mattox with camera used in Alumni Magazine (neg), May 15, 1954 (Box 3)
  - John Mattox with camera on knee (neg) (Box 3)
  - John Mattox, director of Air Force R.O.T.C. Glee Club at WPTF (neg), May 25, 1954 (Box 3)
  - John Mattox in Visual Aids Office (neg), Aug 22, 1960 (Box 3)
  - John Mattox in Visual Aids Office (Print), Aug 22, 1960 (Box 3)
  - John Mattox with camera at Border Belt test farm near Whiteville, N.C. (Print), Aug 6, 1953 (Box 3)
  - John Mattox with camera at Border Belt test farm near Whiteville, N.C. (neg), Aug 6, 1953 (Box 3)
  - John Mattox at desk with camera, Visual Aids Department, Ricks Hall (neg) (Box 3)
  - John Mattox hanging from derrick in reactor (neg), March 31, 1958 (Box 3)
  - John Mattox dressed as a girl photographer at College Union Banquet NCSU (neg), Sept 17, 1954 (Box 3)
  - NCSU Air Force Glee Club at Radio Station WPFF (neg), May 17, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Man plowing near Shotwell (neg), March 30, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Scenic - Mountain, Barn, Mule plowing (neg) (Box 3)
  - Old Yates Mill - ordered by Professor Dan Barnes, School of Design (neg), Sept 30, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Mary Yionoulis & Baby (neg), Oct 13, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Good Mountain Scenes (neg), Aug 2, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Mountain Farm Scenes (Print), 1956 (Box 3)
  - Mountain Farm Scenes (neg), 1956 (Box 3)
  - County Seat - Madison Co. Marshall, N.C. (neg), Sept 25, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Nathan Watson Sr. Lespeoliza hay stacks (neg), Nov 1, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Old Mill at Trenton, N.C, with Spanish moss (neg), March 25, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Picking Cotton (neg), Oct 5, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Old Tobacco barn near Raleigh Country Club area, Clint Williams putting log in his tobacco barn furnace (neg), Sept 1954 (Box 3)
  - Dr. Hudson in campus lab, NCSU (neg), March 30, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Jim Higgins and Douglas at State College track meet (neg), April 27, 1955 (Box 3)
  - State Fair scenes (neg), Oct 1952 (Box 3)
  - Ann Cornelison portrait, Engineering Placement Office (Print) (Box 3)
  - Ann Cornelison portrait, Engineering Placement Office (neg), Oct 29, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Y.W.C.A "colored woman" (neg), Oct 1970 (Box 3)
  - J.C. Jones, Navy Captain unform (neg), Aug 2, 1972 (Box 3)
  - J.C. Jones, Navy Captain unform (Print), Aug 2, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Jean Vincent Portrait Thompson Theatre (Print), March 24, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Jean Vincent Portrait Thompson Theatre (neg), March 24, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Murl Griffin Portrait (neg), June 12, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Murl Griffin Portrait (Print), March 12, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Pat Barefoot Portrait, make-up by Jean Vincent of Thompson Theatre, Freshman Engineering Office (Print), April 17, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Pat Barefoot Portrait (neg), April 17, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Pat Barefoot, "Miss Southern" (Print), Jan 31, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Pat Barefoot, "Miss Southern" (neg), Jan 31, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Debbie McMullan, Freshman student (Print), April 17, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Debbie McMullan, Freshman student (neg), April 17, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Judy Todd Portrait (neg), Oct 1970 (Box 3)
  - Judy Todd Portrait (Print), Oct 1970 (Box 3)
  - Roddy Price, portrait for music building (neg), Feb 20, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Roddy Price, portrait for music building (Print), Feb 20, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Celia Parsons, student portrait, Miss University contest (Print), Sept 14, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Celia Parsons, student portrait, Miss University contest (neg), Sept 14, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Landscape, lab, flower (color neg) (Box 3)
  - Office pictures, Ricks Hall (neg) (Box 3)
  - Unidentified group photo outside Dorton Arena (color neg), circa 1960s (Box 3)
  - NCSU Football (color neg), circa 1960s (Box 3)
  - Maid Marris (neg), circa 1963 (Box 3)
  - Mary C. Southerland portrait (neg), Oct 24, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Frankie B. Crumpler portrait (Print), Oct 24, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Frankie B. Crumpler portrait (neg), Oct 24, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Wide angle view out at office telephone, visual aids (neg), March 1962 (Box 3)
  - Bowling Alley Fire (across from campus) (Prints), March 5, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Bowling Alley Fire (across from campus) (neg), March 5, 1959 (Box 3)
  - "Negroes Picking Cotton" (neg), 1953 (Box 3)
  - Ape with little man at sideshow, State Fair (neg), Oct 1954 (Box 3)
  - Ape with little man at sideshow, State Fair (Print), Oct 1954 (Box 3)
  - Herring Fishing - Columbia, Edenton, etc. (Print), March 1963 (Box 3)
  - Cotton Gin, Zebulon, N.C. (neg), Oct 12, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Cotton Gin, Zebulon, N.C. (Print), Oct 12, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Air Force ROTC Glee Club at tower (neg), May 25, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Person Test negatives, Oct 1974 (Box 3)
  - Mrs. Neal & Shirley, Visual Aids Office (neg), 1956 (Box 3)
  - Mrs. Neal & Mary Yionoulis (neg), Oct 1959 (Box 3)
  - Beef Cattle Barn (neg), April 1952 (Box 3)
  - NCSU Campus Buildings (neg), April 1, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Carolyn Jessup Portrait, Dean of Women (neg), Dec 12, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Carolyn Jessup Portrait, Dean of Women (Print), Dec 12, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Dance - spotlight on scene (Print), April 30, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Dance - spotlight on scene (neg), April 30, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Official Board Meeting at Meredith College (neg), Feb 28, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Bob Bryan in Office (neg) (Box 3)
  - Dr. Hester seminar (zoology), Clark building (neg), Jan 5, 1967 (Box 3)
  - School Design Exhibit, Mr. Randall in Green House (neg), 1957 (Box 3)
  - College Scenes & around Raleigh, Fayetteville St, labs, class scenes (neg), 1954 (Box 3)
  - Sweet Potato Blossom (neg), circa 1965 (Box 3)
  - College scenes - John's desk, dark room, labs, greenhouse (neg), Feb 1953 (Box 3)
  - College scenes (neg), March 14, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Sea Foods, South Port, N.C. (neg), Sept 8, 1967 (Box 3)
  - College Scenes - Court in front of Patterson, Reactor from rear, walls to Dining Hall (neg), Nov 7, 1952 (Box 3)
  - Test negatives - Mrs. Neal, etc. (neg), July 4, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Swannanoa 4H Camp, Photographic Class Group (neg), Aug 10, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Susam Stoleer(?) Agricultural Engineering Expert (neg), May 6, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Dr. H.W. Ganer(?) Portrait (neg), May 30, 1967 (Box 3)
  - J.W. Cash - Wendell, N.C, 101 Tobacco (neg), June 21, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Carolyn Painter Portrait (Print), Jan 18, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Carolyn Painter Portrait (neg), Jan 18, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Sallie Bizzle Portrait (neg), Aug 2, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Mary Lou Phillips Portrait (neg), Sept 2, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Robert P. Bryan Portrait (neg), March 2, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Robert P. Bryan Portrait (Print), March 2, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Ada Della Pozza Portrait (neg) (Box 3)
  - Ada Della Pozza Portrait (Print) (Box 3)
  - Reginald Stroud Portrait (neg), Oct 8, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Elwood Mintz in his office at Department of Agriculture (Print), Oct 22, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Elwood Mintz in his office at Department of Agriculture (neg), Oct 22, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Woodrow Smith Farm - Pool Rd Tobacco Fields (neg), Aug 10, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Smith Farm Pasture Irrigation (neg), Oct 13, 1954 (Box 3)
  - College Tower (neg), Oct 5, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Bronze plaque at corner of Baylord & Morgan St. (Print), Oct 23, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Bronze plaque at corner of Baylord & Morgan St. (neg), Oct 23, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Number 1 dormitory from west side, plumbing being removed (neg), Feb 17, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Dr. Jim Woodburn(?) with Chinese Grad Student in lab (neg) (Box 3)
  - Mrs. Neal and Ralph Mills (neg), Feb 17, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Riddick Building (neg), July 1952 (Box 3)
  - Student Union and New Library under construction (neg), Sept 3, 1952 (Box 3)
  - Barn at Beef Cattle Farm, N.C. State College (neg), April 25, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Page Pate, Engineering Placement Office, Portraits: Rudolphe (wife), Mrs. Page Pate (neg) (Box 3)
  - Tobacco Fields, Mr. R.D. Buchan, Rt. 3 Henderson, N.C. (Print), Aug 2, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Tobacco Fields, Mr. R.D. Buchan, Rt. 3 Henderson, N.C. (neg), Aug 2, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Physics, Glass Blower (neg), Oct 1969 (Box 3)
  - College Union - Porch Construction (neg), July 13, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Beef Cattle Barn, newly covered with aluminum (neg), Nov 14, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Ice on tree at Central State Farm snow and ice storm (neg), Feb 15, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Governor Hodges at desk in Capitol (neg), Feb 17, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Truck Driver Training School, NCSU (neg), March 1954 (Box 3)
  - Music Department - Big Drum, Drum Major sitting on top (neg), Oct 23, 1957 (Box 3)
  - New Riddick Building Doorway (neg), July 18, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Lynn Tullock, Rhododendrons (Print), Feb 21, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Lynn Tullock, Rhododendrons (neg), Feb 21, 1962 (Box 3)
  - State Fair Coliseum (Dorton Arena) (neg), Sept 19, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Shirley Marshall, Visual Aids - Section, Ricks Hall (neg), July, 7, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Conference at Manteo, Trip to Outer Banks with older 4-H group (neg) (Box 3)
  - Mountain Farm Scene, Burley tobacco section near Asheville (Print), 1956 (Box 3)
  - Mountain Farm Scene, Burley tobacco section near Asheville (neg), 1956 (Box 3)
  - New Yacht at Elmer Willis (Williston, N.C.) (neg), March 25, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Mrs. Neal in office (neg) (Box 3)
  - Fishing scene, Morehead City (Print), circa 1970 (Box 3)
  - Fishing scene, Morehead City (neg), circa 1970 (Box 3)
  - Cattle Photographs, State Fair (neg), Oct 1966 (Box 3)
  - Dance, Coliseum (Print), April 25, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Dance, Coliseum (neg), April 25, 1959 (Box 3)
  - College Union Stage, The Formations (Dance Orchestra) (Print), Sept 4, 1968 (Box 3)
  - College Union Stage, The Formations (Dance Orchestra) (neg), Sept 4, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Cooling Fountain (neg), Nov 10, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Cooling Fountain (Print), Nov 10, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Ralph Mills & Douglas Morgan making movies of arrival of uranium for reactor (neg), Sept 3, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Ralph Mills & Douglas Morgan making movies of arrival of uranium for reactor (Print), Sept 3, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Dr. Stuckey in Primrose Hall (neg), Oct 7, 1952 (Box 3)
  - Morehead City area (neg), Dec 8, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Mary Yionoulis portrait (neg), Dec 31, 196(?) (Box 3)
  - Douglas with Dr. Gene Hester at College (neg), Jan 11, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Agriculture Open House (neg), Nov 4, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Agriculture Open House (neg), Nov 4, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Picture exhibit at NC State Library (neg), May 21, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Agriculture Open House (neg), Oct 4, 1961 (Box 3)
  - College Tower from South (neg), June 1, 1953 (Box 3)
  - J.S. Khalson (Print), April 26, 1965 (Box 3)
  - J.S. Khalson (neg), April 26, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Agriculture Open House (neg), Oct 4, 1961 (Box 3)
  - J.E. Smith, King N.C. - cattle and covered wagon (neg) (Box 5)
  - College Union Building at Night - NC State (Print), June 12, 1956 (Box 5)
  - College Union Building at Night - NC State (neg), June 12, 1956 (Box 5)
  - Kit Carson Engine & Small Steam Tractor, Trautman, NC (neg), Oct 19, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Eloise Nowell, Altrusa Club, Velvet Cloak Hotel (neg), Oct 24, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Smokey Area with Two Men, Plant at Morehead City (neg) (Box 5)
  - Smokey Area with Two Men, Plant at Morehead City (Print) (Box 5)
  - Kit Carson Engine & Small Steam Tractor, Trautman, NC (Print), Oct 19, 1961 (Box 5)
  - House on Fire made from Warick Slide (neg), 1955 (Box 5)
  - College Buildings - Library, Tower steps, Administration Building front entrance (Print), March 20, 1953 (Box 5)
  - College Buildings - Library, Tower steps, Administration Building front entrance (neg), March 20, 1953 (Box 5)